Policewoman, nurse, girl student you're my preys
女警 護士 女高中生 全都是我的獵物
I wanna hunt you
我要狩獵你們
I found it
被我發現了
Exellent! we catch it
太好了，趕上了
The toilets at school the western style, too bad
學校儘是些西式洗手間 太糟糕了
I like Japanese styles
還不如和式的好
Are you sure?
看來也不見得
This is evil spirit
這是妖氣
Shit! where're the goblins?
可惡的妖魔到哪去了
They ran away
哎呀哎呀，跑掉了
Someone found us?
剛才的人類有注意到我們嗎
It seems it's too late we allay our spirit
好像是 我們太晚消除自己的氣了
But that girl is very cute
不過那女孩真是可愛
What should we do next? master
要怎麼辦呢？主人？
Devour it, of course
當然是吃下來了
But do it later
不過要等到以後
The dinner tonight is done
今天的晚餐已經準備好了
This smell is too strong
這個內褲味道好嗆哦
It's easy to find a strong smell
這個味道濃，很好找的
It's before menstruation
生理期前的樣子
Yes it can entertain us after dinner
是呀 這下子吃飯後的娛樂增加了
Hurry up, Guizi
京子，動作快點
You're always late
你總是上那麼久
I got it it's soon
我知道啦 很快就好了啦
My God
真是
All are in use
全部使用中
We have no other ways
既然這樣就沒辦法了
Where're you going?
你想上哪去
Wanna get it behind a tree?
你不會是想 隨便找個樹叢解決吧
I'll call the police
那麼做我就喊員警來
Who're you?
你是什麼人呀
I am the queen of hot-rodding
我是賽車女王
And I am his attendant, rightMaster?
然後我是他的隨從 對吧主人
What's this?
這是什麼東西呀
You're so rude what did you call me?
怎麼可以這麼失禮 喊我什麼東西
I am a veteran servant for two thousand years
我是有兩千年 工作資歷的老練僕人
It's ok
不過無所謂
If you don't like this
你若不喜歡我這模樣
I can't recover my face
我就恢復成我的老樣子
It's dirty
哎呀哎呀，太髒了吧
You're...
你到底是。。。
I am Ruttish Satan to suck your spirit
我是淫魔 來接收你的精氣
Yes, once someone is obsessed with master's magic
好耶，只要中了主人的淫術
No woman can resist it
什麼樣的女人都會擋不住
Be careful about a cold
著涼了就不好了
It'd better to turn off now
還是趕快脫掉吧
Guizi, you're so slow today
京子，今天怎麼這麼慢
Don't interrupt
你別礙事
You're a policewoman but you're airing with this dress
你是女警 卻這個模樣開車在城裏兜風
It's shameful
太丟人了
It's you who command to me to do this
是你命令我 要我這麼做的啊
How do you like it? Is it good?
怎麼樣？舒服嗎？
It's good
舒服
What's wrong?
怎麼了？
That red light?
那個。。。紅綠燈。。。
Is it? Wanna give up?
是嗎？不想搞了嗎
Don't stop
不要停止
I wanna fuck you now
現在起 我只在你開車時搞你
How about this?
怎麼這樣
Stop as you see a red light
要是見到紅燈就停下來
Good, Guizi
很好哦，京子
Please hurry up
求求你，快一點
You're cute, Guizi
你很可愛哦，京子
It's great
好棒
Well... I...
那個。。。我。。。
You did it by yourseld?
你一個人搞吧
Please
求求你
Can you drive in this way?
喂，你這樣真的能開車嗎
But...
可是。。。
It's dangerous let others do it
很危險的，換人開車吧
This is so great
這裏好爽呀
What're you doing?
幹什麼
No, why?
不要，為什麼
Free my hands
放開我的手
Get other useful tools?
其他還有沒有可以使用的東西
And this bar and pipe
還有警棍與哨子
This gauge is good
這粗度剛剛好
Do you often use it to jerk?
平時你該不會用這個自慰吧
Never
我沒有用過那個
Why?
為什麼呢
I will break up with it
用那種東西我會裂開的
So you used it before
這麼說你想過要用它咯
Try it prove me you'll break up
那就來試試是不是 真的會讓你裂開
No, don't use it
不要，不要這個
Stop! It's too thick
住手，太粗了啦
No, it's gorgeous
不行，太爽了
Plung this stuff here
快點把東西插進這裏吧
So I can plung mine into yours
這麼說 插進我的粗東西也沒問題了
Ok, master
迪亞比 好的，主人
It's hot
好熱，什麼東西出來了
I enter your body
你只是被我貫穿了而已
Blow this pipe
吹這個哨子吧
No, I can't it's a shame
不要，我辦不到，好丟臉
Don't want it?
真的不要嗎
It's exellent
太棒了
It's noisy
吵死了
How about my blow job?
我的兜風技巧如何
Great! Great!
好棒好棒
See?
你看看。。。
No, Stop don't frighten me
不要，住手，不要拍
Let them see you, slut!
讓他們看光你淫亂的樣子
Stop
住手
They're looking
他們還在看呢
So many people see you, slut
那麼多男人 在看你淫亂的模樣哦
No no
不要，不要
Don't look
不要看啊
I feel extremely high
我快高潮了
Let them see it Guizi
讓大家看你高潮的樣子吧 京子
No, don't shoot
不要，怎們能這樣，不可以高潮啊
How about this meal? Master
這一頓滋味怎麼樣，主人
It's dense and spicy
粘稠的口感中 另有辛辣的底味
It's delicious, Diana
相當好吃哦，迪亞比
The master is really lucky
主人有口福喔
I like the virgin taste
我最喜歡吃處女的甜美味道
I can't find it until now
找了這麼久還找不到
No, I am confused
是我搞錯了嗎
No, it's impossible
不，不可能有那種事
No matter where you hide
不管躲在哪裡
I must find you
我都一定要找出來
Sister
姐姐
Take it easy Angiya
安潔，放輕鬆吧
Angiya, don't call my sister before Luther Father
安潔，不可在新來的 路德神父面前喊我姐姐哦
Men will be erected after seeing a huge chest
女人乳房有了男人後會變大
Why are yours so big?
為什麼沒有經驗的你 乳房會這麼大呢
Because Liliya sister caress my breast everyday
因為莉莉婭姐姐每天摸我
Sister
姐姐
Both men and women can caress. It's effective
原來不論男人摸女人摸 效果都是一樣的
No, sister
不是的，姐姐
I am kidding take it easy
騙你的，別那麼認真
Let me try it
柔軟的乳房
Don't give Luther any chance
不可以給路德機會哦
Don't bite the nipples will be erect
你這樣咬，乳頭會尖立的
Suck it I'll...
這樣吸，我會。。。我會。。。
And then
會怎麼樣呢
Sister I am so high very high
姐姐，我快高潮了，快高潮餓
Angiya
安潔
Luther Father
路德神父
Are you Angiya?
你是安潔吧
I need your help
我有事想請你幫忙
Can you come here?
來一下好嗎
Yes
是
For what?
請問找我什麼事呢
This room is closed?
這個房間不是不能打開的嗎
It's opened
打開了
Luther Father, this is...
路德大人，這到底是。。。
I saw it last night
昨夜我看到
Your behaviors betray God
你們做了違背神意的行為
It's not true
那不是真的
Angiya, your attitude...
安潔，你拿出這個態度
I can't save you if someone found you're a witch
萬一被人懷疑你是魔女 我也很難救你哦
Witch?
魔女
It's like this...
比如這個？
Pick up a teeth with it
用這個拔牙
Pick up a nail
拔指甲
Confess it
你還不承認時
Break those fingers
就把指頭一根一根折斷
Luther Father, I did nothing evil
路德神父，我沒做什麼壞事的
No, no, no
不要，不要，不要
Is it? Admit you're a witch
是嗎？你承認你是魔女了嗎
Angiya
安潔
Angiya is not here
安潔也不在這裏
Where's she going?
她是跑哪兒去了？
It's not your fault
要怪不該怪你
It's Liliya's
應該怪莉莉婭
Sister? Is it real?
姐姐？真的嗎？
Yes, Liliya is a witch
沒錯，莉莉婭一定是魔女
Angiya
安潔
That's great
好棒，好棒哦
Yours are all explored
你的性感帶似乎都開發了
It’s Angiya's lecture
大概受過莉莉婭不少教導
Sister...
姐姐。。。
Men are so cute
原來男人是這麼令人爽的東西
No
不要
Luther... you're...
路德，你竟然。。。
Don't misunderstand it
請別誤會
Angiya wanna get rid of a witch's bound
安潔是為了 逃脫魔女的束縛而戰的
A witch?
魔女？
It's Angiya
據安潔說
It's you to make her a lesbian
是你帶領她成為同性戀的
Yes, Luther
是的，路德大人
How come? Angiya
怎麼這樣，安潔
Don't insult God
不止冒瀆神明
Wanna make a nun become a witch
還想把修道女教導成魔女
Let Luther purify you sister
姐姐也請路德大人 來為你淨身吧
No, no, no
不要，不要
Water, I need water
水，請給我水喝
Are you thirsty? confess you're a witch
口渴了嗎？ 那就承認自己是魔女吧
Yes, I am
好了，快承認
I don't admit it
我死也不承認
You're so tough
這麼嘴硬
Your body is so hot and sensitive
你的身體這麼熱 這麼的敏感
Stand with only a leg it's painful
只用腳尖站著 一定很痛苦吧
Look water is over there
瞧，水在那邊哦
Your Angiya wants to save you
你的安潔說想救你哦
Wanna water?
想喝水的話
Walk over there
就走到那裏去吧
Monster
禽獸
No, it breaks up
不要，那裏快裂開了
What's wrong? Liliya
怎麼了？莉莉婭
It's just the beginning
現在才剛開始呀
It's God's mercy
沒辦法，這是神的慈悲
Let me help you go further
我來讓你鼓起勇氣向前進吧
What're you talking about?
你說什麼
What?
什麼
Let me stop. I got it
我到了，請讓我停下來
Congratulations good efforts Liliya
恭喜你 你努力的很好，莉莉婭
Don't stop
不行，不可以停下來
No, Angiya don't move
不行，安潔，不可以動
Please, move move it
求求你，動呀，動呀
How come...
怎麼這樣。。。
Angiya
安潔
Sister
姐姐
Human will is so strong
人體還真是堅固啊
Trig your weight with the breast only
只靠乳房就能支撐體重
Don't you think so? Liliya
你不這麼認為嗎？莉莉婭
Angiya
安潔
What do you want?
你想做什麼
Liliya! You're emulative
莉莉婭，你很好勝
It will be my shame in this way
這樣下去我會沒面子的
Confess it there's no ways
沒辦法，在你自己承認之前
I wanna torture this girl's beautiful body
我就折磨這女孩美麗的身體
Angiya
安潔
What do you want?
你想做什麼
Stop it, please stop it
住手，求求你，請你住手
Angiya is innocent
安潔是無辜的
I wanna torture you
要折磨就找我
Stop it, please!
住手，求求你
Stop, please!
求求你住手
Angiya
安潔
What do you want?
你想要做什麼
Free me
饒了我
Please let me go
求求你饒了我
Stop please
住手，求求你
Please free me, please
求求你，求求你饒了我
It's me to make Angiya racy
是我讓安潔變成淫亂的女人
Please, it's enough
饒了我，饒了我，我受夠了
Why? I said I am a witch
為什麼 我已經承認我是魔女了
And then, eat my penis stick it
那麼就含住我神聖的陽具 表示誠意，舔吧
Since you've confessed you're a witch get this print
那麼，既然你承認自己是魔女 就得接受這個烙印
Stop
住手
I am dying, please stop it
求求你，住手，我會死的
And, it's your turn
接下來換你了
No, I am not a witch
不要，饒了我，我不是魔女
Are you Luther Father a new director of a church
請問您是新到的 教會長路德大人嗎
I am Marry I'll have a wedding festival here
我叫瑪麗 這次要在這個教堂舉行婚禮
So I would like meet you fiirst
所以想先來打招呼